apksfull.com 2015-03-25

# Privacy | ApksFULL

APKsFULL provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of APKsFULL.com (this “Site”) and our Android Marketplace Application.  
This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us through this Site or through our Android Marketplace Application. This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. We will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. You are advised to consult this policy regularly for any changes.

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**

Personal information is data that can be used to identify or contact a single person.

You may be asked to provide your personal information anytime you are in contact with APKsFULL or an APKsFULL Partner. APKsFULL and its Partners may share this personal information with each other and use it consistent with this Privacy Policy. They may also combine it with other information to provide and improve our products, services, content, and advertising. You are not required to provide the personal information that we have requested, but, if you chose not to do so, in many cases we will not be able to provide you with our products or services or respond to any queries you may have.

**Protection of Personal Information**

APKsFULL takes the security of your personal information very seriously. APKsFULL online services protect your personal information during transit using encryption such as Transport Layer Security (TLS). In any case, since the Internet is an open network, you must be aware of the possibility that the information can be intercepted, lost, redirected, changed and read by other people. When your personal data is stored by APKsFULL, we use computer systems with limited access housed in facilities using physical security measures.

When you use some APKsFULL products, services, or applications or post on an APKsFULL forum, public comment, chat room, or social networking service, the personal information you share is visible to other users and can be read, collected, or used by them. You are responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in these instances. For example, if you list your name and email address in a comment posting, that information is public. Please take care when using these features.

**Integrity and Retention of Personal Information**

Android makes it easy for you to keep your personal information accurate, complete, and up to date. We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

You have the right to access your personal data and the right to obtain the rectification, erasure or blocking of the data concerning you, whenever such is justified, by contacting APKsFULL through the e-mail address indicated below.

**International Transfer**

Your information may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction.

**Location-Based Services**

To provide location-based services APKsFULL and our partners may collect, use, and share precise location data, including the real-time geographic location of your computer, tablet, smartphone or device. This location data is collected anonymously in a form that does not personally identify you and is used by APKsFULL and our partners to provide and improve location-based products and services. For example, we may share geographic location with application providers when you opt in to their location services.

**  
Log Data**

When you visit the Site, whether as a APKsFULL Member or a non-registered user just browsing (any of these, a “APKsFULL User”), our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type or the webpage you were visiting before you came to our Site, pages of our Site that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our Site, access times and dates, and other statistics. We use this information to monitor and analyze use of the Site and the Service and for the Site’s technical administration, to increase our Site’s functionality and user-friendliness, and to better tailor it to our visitors’ needs.

**  
Cookies**

Like many websites, we use “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer, smartphone or tablet, for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies for two purposes. First, we utilize persistent cookies to save your registration ID and login password for future logins to the Site or Mobile Application. Second, we utilize session ID cookies to enable certain features of the Site or Mobile Application, to better understand how you interact with the Site or Mobile Application and to monitor aggregate usage by APKsFULL Users and web traffic routing on the Site or Mobile Application. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted from your computer when you log off from the Site or Mobile Application and Service. Third party advertisers on the Site or Mobile Application may also place or read cookies on your browser. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Site or Mobile Application or all functionality of our Services.

**  
Phishing**

Identity theft and the practice currently known as “phishing” are of great concern to APKsFULL. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, your account ID, login password, or any identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication.

**  
Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:  
APKsFULL@gmail.com

Effective Dec 15, 2014
